<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PPBank2.0</string>
    <string name="mail">mail</string>
    <string name="login">login</string>
    <string name="forget_password">forget password?</string>
    <string name="register">register?</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="income">income</string>
    <string name="expense">expense</string>
    <string name="balance">"balance  $ "</string>
    <string name="expense_apply">Expense Apply</string>
    <string name="prize_apply">Prize Apply</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">[User Terms / Legal Affairs] Privacy Policy Customer trust is the most important basis for the company to provide services. The company attaches great importance to the privacy of members\' individuals, and follows the relevant laws and regulations on the protection of privacy and personal data. The following is the company\'s privacy policy (hereinafter referred to as \"this policy\"). ㄧ About the company The company referred to in this policy refers to Millimeter International Co., Ltd. (referred to as \"Homie Lab\" or \"the company\"); the group referred to. If you have any questions about this policy or wish to contact the company, please feel free to write to homoielab@gmail.com. Second, other agreements This policy should be updated with the company\'s \"Member User Terms\" or the company at any time. 更 New supplements, the terms of the agreement that are in effect at that time are complementary to each other. If there is any conflict, regarding the privacy of the customer and For personal data related matters, this policy should be applied with priority. 3. The company may collect personal data about you. Personal data can be used to identify you, but it does not include data that cannot identify individuals (regardless of the data, it is not possible to identify individuals or to identify them). After personalized processing 理, no person can be identified or the analysis data generated by the company after processing 理 personal data). Here are the explanations: (1) Personal information that you provide to the company A. Identity information 1. In order to register as a member of the company and use the services provided by the company, the company may require you to provide your name and information. Year of birth, date of month, identity certificate documents (for example, such as identity card, health insurance card, or front and back image electronic file of driver\'s license), number of identity card number, mobile phone number, email address, Community information and / or characteristics or preferences about you. However, our company will not collect the special personal data (example 例 such as: medical records, medical treatment, genetics) specified in Article 6 of your Personal Data Protection Law. Because of the different services you use, the personal information you need to provide may also be different. 2. Depending on the services you use, we may need to collect different personal information. Example: For example, if you use the company\'s login service, the company needs you to provide the information required to log in to the Internet, the bank, and the bank, such as the ID number, user code, and password. The login information required for each bank may differ. You do not have to use a proxy login service. Under the open banking 行 framework, you have more choices. For example, if you can authorize our company to directly use the Application Programming Interfaces (API) to connect to the bank account 行User information, but the scope of the information obtained by the link will be limited by the laws and regulations and the cooperation bank 行 openness at the time. B. Linked information is for providing services (such as  transactions such as bank transfers, payment, records, credits, financial merchandise shopping guides, credit ratings, etc.), participation, rewards or promotional activities, or intentions to see feedback needs. You may need to obtain your contact information, including but not limited to telephone, e-mail address, communication software account, etc. C. Financial information and transactions 易 data 1. Depending on the services you use, the company may obtain your account balance, account balance in the financial institution with your consent and compliance with regulations Financial information or other financial information. 2. The transaction 易 information also includes the car number, serial number, deposit account number, credit card information, telecommunication fee bill, water bill, fuel bill that you need to provide to use the payment function Bills, parked cars, fee bills and other bills and all personal information contained on the bills. 3. Depending on the content of the selected service, you may conduct 行 ⾦ gold 金 rong transactions 易 in different scenarios. The company may need to obtain information about your transactions 易 to provide specific services. D. Consumption and advertising preferences To improve the consumer experience, the company may collect your preferences for consumption and advertising. If you refuse to provide, you can still use most of the company\'s services, but you may be told that you cannot use certain services.</string>

    <string name="account_nmanagement">Account\nmanagement</string>
    <string name="mobile_npayment">Mobile\npayment</string>
    <string name="commit">commit</string>
    <string name="number_of_remaining_award_applications">Number of remaining award applications:</string>
    <string name="type">Type</string>
    <string name="apply_money">Apply money</string>
    <string name="remakes">Remakes</string>
    <string name="prove">prove</string>
    <string name="signout">signout</string>
    <string name="parent">parent</string>
    <string name="child">child</string>
    <string name="recent_records">Recent records</string>
    <string name="more">more</string>
    <string name="transfer_nmoney">Transfer\nmoney</string>
    <string name="buy_something">buy something</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>

    <string name="account">account</string>
    <string name="remark">remark</string>

    <string name="save">save</string>
    <string name="name">name</string>
    <string name="content">content</string>
    <string name="money">money</string>
    <string name="password">password</string>
    <string name="add_task">Add Task</string>
    <string name="notify">notify</string>
    <string name="clock">clock</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>

    <string name="apply">apply</string>
    <string name="task">task</string>
    <string name="prize">prize</string>
    <string name="pocketmoney">pocket money</string>
    <string name="sum">sum</string>
    <string name="food">food</string>
    <string name="dailysupplies">dailysupplies</string>
    <string name="entertainment">entertainment</string>
    <string name="other">other</string>
    <string name="Budgetbalance">Budgetbalance</string>
    <string name="expenditure" >expenditure</string>
    <string name="budget">budget</string>
    <string name="Immediatetasks">Immediate tasks</string>
    <string name="Dailytasks">Daily tasks</string>
    <string name="Addimmediatetask">Add immediate task</string>
    <string name="Adddailytask">Add daily task</string>
    <string name="limit">Up to 300 for a single apply</string>

</resources>
